<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>72546</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>CSI|CSI: Las Vegas</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/72546-g13.jpg</banner>
<Overview>CSI is a crime drama in which the characters use cutting-edge forensic tools to examine the evidence to solve the case.  Rather than asking 'whodunnit' (investigating witnesses/suspects), CSI explores the 'howdunnit'.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2000-10-06</FirstAired>
<Network>CBS</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0247082</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP00380341</zap2it_id>
<id>72546</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73696</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>CSI: NY</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>CSI: New York</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/73696-g4.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The third edition of the "CSI" franchise sets up shop in the Big Apple, where taciturn Detective Mac Taylor (Gary Sinise) and his partner, Detective Stella Bonasera (Melina Kanakaredes), lead a crime-solving team. Like his counterparts in Las Vegas and Miami, Taylor knows that people may lie, but the evidence rarely does.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2004-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>CBS</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0395843</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP00679714</zap2it_id>
<id>73696</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>253030</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Jurassic CSI</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Jurassic C.S.I.</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/253030-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>In Jurassic CSI, dino detective Dr. Phil Manning launches a full-scale investigation to unearth how dinosaurs really looked and lived. 

Jurassic CSI goes into the minds, under the skin and inside the bones of the biggest, most impressive beasts ever to walk the planet. Dr. Manning doesn’t stick to convention – or even his own discipline – on his perpetual quest to expand what we know about dinosaurs. With privileged access to some of the world’s most sophisticated technologies – from crime scene 3D mapping technology to an image machine one million times stronger than a chest X-ray – Jurassic CSI challenges long – held assumptions and poses radical questions about our understanding of dinosaurs.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-09-15</FirstAired>
<Network>National Geographic (US)</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1945727</IMDB_ID>
<id>253030</id>
</Series>
</Data>