<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>279867</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Down East Dickering</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/279867-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Welcome to Maine and the world of dickering, where everything comes with a price tag. Using a weekly publication, Uncle Henry's, as a guide, our expert dickerers make a good enough living in swapping, buying, and selling, to enjoy life on their own terms. Tony Bennett and his partner, Codfish, turn a hefty profit on vintage auto parts and soda signs. Roland "Yummy" Raubeson and his son Mitchell tackle a bridge-building project. And Clint Rohdin and his future son-in-law Nate trade mechanical skills and hard labor for the perfect demolition derby junker. Just a normal week in Down East Maine!</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-04-02</FirstAired>
<Network>History</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3762958</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01887989</zap2it_id>
<id>279867</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>261448</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Ruth Rendell's Thirteen Steps Down</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/261448-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview> Mix Cellini is a lonely young man who is employed by a company that repairs exercise equipment. He lives in a flat of an old Victorian house in Notting Hill. His reclusive landlady, Gwendoline Chawcer, spends her time reading and thinking about lost loves. Mix becomes obsessed with serial killer John Christie and a local model, Nerissa Nash, despite the fact that she never acknowledges his existence.
</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-08-13</FirstAired>
<Network>ITV1</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2336352</IMDB_ID>
<id>261448</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>277738</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Don't look down</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/277738-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>This documentary follows James Kingston, an urban free climber who scales 100m cranes, 200m radio towers, tall buildings and bridges... without using any safety equipment at all</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-01-19</FirstAired>
<Network>Channel 4</Network>
<id>277738</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>273675</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Man Down</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/273675-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Dan is a childish idiot trapped in an adult’s life, whose world is at near collapse.
His girlfriend Naomi is fast running out of patience with his inability to navigate the simplest of life tasks. He has two uniquely dysfunctional friends and a listless teaching career that sees him begrudgingly teach a version of the same lesson every day, inexplicably popular with all but one of the pupils, with his only highlight coming in the form of Miss Lipsey, a head mistress who views Dan with a mixture of pity and despair.
To make matters worse, he is tormented daily by his willfully insane father, whose driving motivation in life seems to be to ensure his son is humiliated at every turn.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2013-10-18</FirstAired>
<Network>Channel 4</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3063454</IMDB_ID>
<id>273675</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>286076</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>My Momma Throws Down</SeriesName>
<Overview>Women compete in cooking challenges while members of their families cheer them on.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-05-04</FirstAired>
<Network>TV One</Network>
<id>286076</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>83355</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Down and Dirty with Jim Norton</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/83355-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>From the stage of the Bergen Performing Arts Center in New Jersey, Jim Norton – along with series deejay Lemmy from Motörhead – welcomes some of the country's top comics to perform their most outrageous adults-only routines in front of a raucous overflow audience. Headliners include Artie Lange, Andrew "Dice" Clay, Bill Burr and Patrice O'Neal – party on!</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-10-03</FirstAired>
<Network>HBO</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1239394</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01084125</zap2it_id>
<id>83355</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73486</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Down to Earth (1995)</SeriesName>
<Overview>Down to Earth was a comedy series created by John Esmonde and Bob Larbey. The series starred Richard Briers as Tony Fairfax, a former cultural attaché for a Latin American country who finds life hard when he returns to life in the United Kingdom.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1995-01-05</FirstAired>
<Network>BBC One</Network>
<id>73486</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73945</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Down to Earth (1984)</SeriesName>
<Overview>The premise of this fondly remembered sitcom from the '80s, which ran on WTBS (before they dropped the "W") was best summed up with some words from the theme song... "Back in the days of Valentino, we know a maid named Ethyl was so bright and alive. But she was struck down by a trolley, golly; said goodbye in nineteen-twenty-and-five. Ethyl in Heaven awaited patiently to earn her wings and be an angel fancy free.  Sixty years later the opportunity to help a family came. Back down to Earth to teach the Prestons lessons -- Richard, Lissy, Dwayne, and J.J. too..." In an attempt to earn her wings, Ethel is placed with the Preston family, where she acts as maid.  Richard Preston, a widower and realtor, is the head of the clan.  Duane is the class-conscious teenage son and Lissy is the teenage daughter.  The youngest of the Preston clan is J.J., the only one who knows that Ethel is an angel, since she was the answer to his prayers.   Over the years, there were a number of cast</Overview>
<FirstAired>1984-03-01</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo Broadcasting System</Network>
<id>73945</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82467</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Eastbound &amp; Down</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/82467-g6.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Relief Pitcher Kenny Powers was poised to rule the Big Leagues, but two things got in his way: his fading fastball and his insufferable personality.  After a spectacular career flame-out, Kenny came home to Shelby, NC and picked up a job as a substitute gym teacher (mostly so his brother Dustin would stop threatening to kick him out).  He's spent every moment since then cashing in the last of his dying fame while plotting his inevitable comeback...one beer at a time.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-02-15</FirstAired>
<Network>HBO</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0866442</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH01118413</zap2it_id>
<id>82467</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>276163</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Party Down South</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/276163-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>From the producers of “Jersey Shore” comes a new series follows eight young, brazen adults for one wild summer of extreme fun. Their summer vacation spot, Murrells Inlet, South Carolina, may never be the same after these fast friends work, party and bond with one another over their common love of the South. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-01-16</FirstAired>
<Network>CMT</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3454468</IMDB_ID>
<id>276163</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>285786</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Voyage of Emperor Qian Long to Jiang Nan</SeriesName>
<Network>CCTV</Network>
<id>285786</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>257963</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers - Runnin Down A Dream</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/257963-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>"Runnin' Down A Dream," a film directed by cinema legend Peter Bogdanovich, is the story of one of America's great rock and roll bands told as never before.
</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-10-14</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0965382</IMDB_ID>
<id>257963</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>248238</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>NZSAS: First Among Equals</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>SAS Down Under</AliasNames>
<Overview>A world first - an exclusive documentary series about the inner workings of this country's most famous fighting elite, the top "1 percenters" of the New Zealand Defense Force - better known as the NZ SAS. For 3 years, award-winning filmmakers Desert Road enjoyed unprecedented and unparalleled access to this world-renowned but never-before-seen Special Force. During this time, Desert Road's cameras followed the unit as they selected a new intake of troopers and, over many gruelling months, moulded these raw soldiers into highly-skilled troopers of NZ SAS calibre, ready to deploy overseas - and participate in the Global War on Terror - at a moment's notice. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-05-24</FirstAired>
<Network>National Geographic (US)</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1332049</IMDB_ID>
<id>248238</id>
</Series>
</Data>